ganttpro.com 2016-04-04

# PRIVACY STATEMENT At ganttpro.com, your privacy protection is our priority. We strive to ensure your protection at all times, in all circumstances. We collect data from you when you register on our site, subscribe to our newsletter, react to a survey or fill out a form. When registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your e-mail address only. HOW DO WE USE THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT? If you become a ganttpro.com user, we ask you to create your account using your social media networks or e-mail address. Your personal information is collected, used and disclosed for purposes including creating an account, personalizing your experience, carrying out or responding to your requests, verifying your identity, improving our website, improving our customer services, communicating with you. Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent. The email address you provide for registering may be used to send you information about recent updates, occasional company news, related product or service information, etc. Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email. GANTT CHARTS DATA AND OUR USE OF LOG FILES We store your Gannt chart data securely and only provide access by your security credentials or

PRIVACY STATEMENT
At ganttpro.com, your privacy protection is our priority. We strive to ensure your protection at all
times, in all circumstances. We collect data from you when you register on our site, subscribe to
our newsletter, react to a survey or fill out a form. When registering on our site, as appropriate,
you may be asked to enter your e-mail address only.
HOW DO WE USE THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT?
If you become a ganttpro.com user, we ask you to create your account using your social media
networks or e-mail address.
Your personal information is collected, used and disclosed for purposes including creating an
account, personalizing your experience, carrying out or responding to your requests, verifying your
identity, improving our website, improving our customer services, communicating with you. Your
information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any
other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent.
The email address you provide for registering may be used to send you information about recent
updates, occasional company news, related product or service information, etc. Note: If at any time
you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe
instructions at the bottom of each email.
GANTT CHARTS DATA AND OUR USE OF LOG FILES
We store your Gannt chart data securely and only provide access by your security credentials or
the security credentials of other GanttPRO’s users you chose to collaborate with. As an application,
GanttPRO stores information on charts saved, descriptions, meta-data and any other associated
information required to provide a useful charting application.
When you visit our site we automatically log your computer's IP address, browser type and access
times. We utilize this information to conduct site performance evaluations, to see where visitors
are coming from and to keep track of click stream data (that is, information about which screens
our users visit on our site). This data helps us to determine what content our members find most
appealing so that we can maximize your enjoyment of the site. Log files are not tied to personally
identifiable information unless required by law. Users who do not register or log in as members
may browse the site without providing any personal information.
HOW DO WE SECURE YOUR INFORMATION?
All ganttpro.com employees are required to take your personal information very seriously. The
information is ID and password protected and our Web security is reviewed regularly. We
implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when
you register, create Gantt charts and collaborate on projects with other GanttPRO’s users.
We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via
Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our payment gateway providers
database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and
are required to keep the information confidential.

To prevent your information from being read or changed while in transit and provide the strongest
privacy and integrity protection we use Hypertext Transfer Protocol Secure (HTTPS).
HOW DO WE USE COOKIES?
Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive
through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to
recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.
We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits.
DO WE DISCLOSE ANY INFORMATION TO OUTSIDE PARTIES?
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable
information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website,
conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information
confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to
comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety.
However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for
marketing, advertising, or other uses.
YOUR CONSENT
By using our site, you consent to our website's privacy policy.
CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will notify you via email.
